Preston Witt Foote

PROFILE

An experienced Service Industry Professional specializing in Product Knowledge, Customer Service and Beer. New to the Traverse City area and ready to branch out into a fun and exciting work environment to grow and learn professionally with progressive, creative and like minded people.

EXPERIENCE

Bartender, Lowbar: Traverse City, MI June — August 2021

-Assisted coworkers to prep for and execute cocktail service and serve charcuterie plates. Roles included taking orders from guests at tables and bar to build and serve, maintaining an effective work flow throughout service, while overseeing payments with cash and card.

Asst. Bar Manager/ Bartender: Wicked Weed Brewing, Asheville, NC — April 2017-May 2021

- -Originally hired as a Bartender, became Assistant Bar Manager in April 2019.
- -Responsible for managing an efficient bar staff during high intensity shifts, while ensuring my fellow Bartenders were happy and productive to encourage responsible alcoholic beverage sales and guarantee an exciting environment for guests to enjoy food and beverages.
- -Contributed recipes and collaborated with bar manager to create seasonally appropriate cocktails for quarterly menus and drink specials.

Tour Guide, Wicked Weed Brewing: Asheville, NC — May 2018 - May 2021

- -Safely facilitated and led Brewery Tours at Wicked Weed's public and commercial locations, meeting Tour Department's goal to educate, host and entertain consumers in an interactive and informative environment to relay company core values and beliefs, while also safely serving alcoholic beverages.
- -My sincere care for the brewery helped relay the culture and core values of the company, showcasing the company's beliefs for valuing it's employees and community, while remaining a profitable business.

Head Server, Bartender, Server Trainer, Bonefish Grill: Asheville, NC — February 2010 - March 2017

-2010, began working for Bonefish Grill location in Southern Pines, NC.

-As Head Server, helped management close the store after hours handling and depositing petty cash into safe, recording daily sales and inventory.

EDUCATION

Student at MSU for Web Development, *Currently Enrolled, Virtual* UNC Pembroke, Pembroke, NC — 2010-12, *No Degree* Pinecrest HS, Southern Pines, NC — 2010, *HS Diploma*

TRAINING AND SKILLS

Diversity & Inclusion Training, March 2019 - Wicked Weed Brewing

TIPS Alcohol Certification, October 2017 - NC Alcoholic Beverage Control (Certificate Valid through October 2021)

Adept Aerosol Paint & Graphic Design Artist

REFERENCES

Russ Brown PUB General Manger, Wicked Brewing, Asheville, NC

Phone: 404-734-3535

Email: Russel.Brown@wickedweedbrewing.com

- Shawn Robinson PUB Bar Manager, Wicked Weed Brewing, Asheville, NC

Phone: 828-974-4471

Email: Shawn.Robinson@wickedweedbrewing.com

Nathan Smith Curator of Culture, Wicked Weed Brewing, Asheville, NC

Phone: 828-335-8289

Email: Nathan.Smith@wickedweedbrewing.com